What's up everyone? Welcome to Milk
Road. What you're going to see today is
a sneak preview of Milk Road Pro After
Hours, which our analysts record after
every single one of our rollup episodes
on this channel. So, basically what they
do is they talk for 40 minutes, record
this beautiful podcast, and then
afterwards, they stick around to
actually talk about their moves and
grill each other on each other's
portfolios, pull up the portfolios and
see what's in there and kind of, you
know, discuss what their moves might
actually be this coming week and into
the future. It's where the real alpha
is. And if you want to see these right
when they come out, you can go Milk Road
Pro for just a dollar at the link below.
They come out right after the episodes,
but the one you're going to see today is
a few weeks old, so keep that in mind.
Otherwise, enjoy it.
>> All right, welcome back after hours.
Hopefully you guys enjoyed the roll up
this week. Now, it is time to talk about
our portfolios. We're going to start
with Melvin, our boy Junior. I think
he's made the most moves uh recently. Um
what's on your mind in your portfolio?
What is the most recent move you made?
Actually, I guess I can see it right
here. You bought some um Credo.
>> Yeah, I bought some Credo because um
they had their earnings about two three
weeks ago and uh stocks still sell off
because they having a little bit of a
deceleration, but that's totally fine.
They're they were going at triple digit
numbers. Um if you don't know what Credo
is, essentially it's basically one of
the companies responsible for moving,
you know, um data around AI uh data
centers. um you know obviously the GPUs
like provides the computing power but
all those GPUs memory system and network
need you know uh constantly need to
communicate with each other and Credo
essentially builds the advanced cables
um that makes these chips connect faster
more reliable and more efficient. Um
their main business or one of their
business is active electric cables.
These are their advanced copper like
cables um connecting all these chips and
switches together. Um, I really like
their earnings. Um, I believe growth,
their growth is expected to slow down
from 115% this quarter to roughly 98%
next quarter. Um, and investors were
looking for a little bit of a larger
guidance increase, which they haven't
done. But you have to understand this
stock had a huge runup this year. I
think the all-time high is somewhere
between 280 or 250 if I'm not mistaken.
300 something 300. Yeah. and it's right
now currently at 150, but I think he has
a good shot of making it past 220 um by
the end of the year, 200s to 220. So, um
when all the doomer stuff happened or
not the doomer stuff, last week we had a
bit of a selloff. Um and yesterday, um
we also had a bit of a sell-off. So, I
this was one stock that hasn't really
moved in the last couple days or last
couple weeks. So, I just decided to buy
it. I I think this is a really good buy.
Um so, yeah. Damn, you bought a 107 back
in March. It ran to 300. No profits you
took. No profits you took.
>> Yeah, [gasps] should have taken some
profits, but it's okay. Um, but I also
last week I want to say I sold some of
my positions. I was um I was getting a
little nervous going into this week,
especially with the Fed rate hikes and
whatnot. Um, last week the there wasn't
much of a chance or there was the
chances were significantly lower. Now
it's around 93%. Um, so I just wanted to
have some cash so I can deploy at times
like this when we have overall market
weakness. So I sold like two grand I
believe in Nebas and I also sold some
meta which happened.
>> Ran on you, didn't it? [laughter]
>> It ran on me. I waited this long. The
next day ran up on me. But that's okay.
That is that is a okay. It's up like 5
to 10% some 10% I believe. So I'm okay
with that. I feel I I can sleep better
at night knowing that I have some cash
position in hand. So,
>> yeah. What do you got in cash? 6,000.
Wow, you really did increase your cash
position. Well done, sir. I did.
>> Um
Oracle. Oracle is an interesting one. Um
this is the the bet on OpenAI and OpenAI
has been on an absolute tear over the
last what like month since July, let's
call it. Um do you think or O or O or O
or O or O or O or O or O or O or O or O
or O oracle has a big comeback? It's
also down like what 50% at least. Yeah,
it it is down 50%. Their OCI increased
um which is their cloud business um
which is the main thing that everybody
really cares about. But the main problem
with Oracle is I think it's also very
much tied to the interest rates as well
because they have a massive massive debt
in on their company. So if interest rate
gets hike or like if there is any major
hikes coming up they're they're going to
be significantly affected by it. Uh but
I do think they have a chance to come
back. I think um their recent quarter
showed um great numbers. Um their
revenues up um and their cloud business
is up. So, I'm not I'm not super
worried. This is a stock you want to buy
and hold for, you know, the next couple
years. You'll you'll you'll easily
double your money here. Like, this is
this is a no-brainer.
>> Yeah. Martin, over to you, buddy. Uh you
you've been uh you added a few things to
your watch list. I is one of them. And
then you also had a couple updates on on
App Leven, your worst performing asset
that you think is going to be your best.
Talk to me about it.
>> Yeah, I think um markets sold off
Applovin because they missed their uh Q2
earnings by 1%. And so they got punished
like uh I think it was huge overreaction
of the market and the management said
that they missed by 1% because they
didn't update the model quickly enough.
Uh so I think it's no it's no issue at
all and they guided for much much higher
growth in in Q3. So I think once we got
Q3 results like the whole all FUD is
going to be just like removed and the
the stock will rerate higher. You took a
bunch of profits last week. We talked
about it last week a little bit. You
have not deployed that again yet. you
were very bearish on our uh rollup that
we just did.
>> Is that why you took profits? And uh
what are you looking at to deploy?
>> I'm not in a hurry to deploy because
again right now I feel like I don't know
if we are uh going uh higher or lower. I
mean like you know yields and Iran and
Trump and like there's just so much
going on and like don't get me wrong I
have just 15% in cash so like I am still
very much allocated to the market so
like you know if I'm bearish I would
probably increase my cash position much
more but um yeah I I want to have some
cash ready if we see like you know
deeper deeper sell off.
>> We're going to pause for a second. The
AI trade is changing. The bottleneck
stocks are either running out of steam
or getting ready for another leg higher
while the application layer is finally
starting to show some real profits. Our
analysts were early to the last wave and
now they are buying for the next one.
Catch your next call inside Milkro Pro
for just a dollar at the link below. But
I added iron to to my watch list because
as you know Galaxy is my biggest
position and last week I was checking
what air uh because aircode was kind of
making announcements about which
companies got some aircott approvals and
some classifications. And I saw that
iron got two gigawatts approved um
classified as conditional base load
which pretty much means like hey guys if
you are going to meet all these
conditions which I suppose they are you
are going to have access to 2 GB and so
they already have pretty much confirmed
access to 5 GW and I think that like you
know access to the energy is going to be
a big thing again and now all these
companies with access to the energy are
priced down pretty heavily and including
Galaxy. I think iron looks really
interesting here. I'm still working on
it, but um yeah, I I'm probably going to
share this next.
>> Yeah, Melvin [clears throat] bought
Iron. Melvin bought some iron a couple
weeks ago, right? You know what my
problem is with Iron? And I haven't done
enough research on them, but they
sponsored the Golden State Warriors at
like the highest I think the highest
amount ever for a basketball team. And
I'm like, you're a B2B like
infrastructure play. Why? Why are you
sponsoring the Golden State Warriors? It
makes no sense.
>> Did you know they sponsored the All-In
podcast or All-In Summit as well
yesterday?
>> Did they? I didn't know that. So, it
just feels a bit rogue. Like, I don't
know that they really need to do any of
that. I understand some of their client
base is is obviously in San Francisco,
so that's why they're doing it. But,
like, there's a lot easier ways to get
to a very small group of people that
they would need to be selling their uh
their compute to. It's just it seems
very odd. But anyway, you can look into
that as you do your research. Uh Martin,
so you're still looking into buy them.
Anyone else you're looking at right now?
>> I also edit Terra Wolf, which is a
similar story, but I haven't done my
full research yet. So, um I want to
finish my Iron uh final thesis first and
then I'll share with everyone else on
the platform and then I will look into
Terra Wolf. By the way, for those um
watching, just before you jump in,
Melvin, uh if you click on the MRMI
inside of the platform, the Milk Road
macro index, you can see the allocations
of of cash that the analysts have. It
totals it all up here, as well as um
what our indicators show in terms of the
market. Um so, right now, uh a few of us
actually have taken out some cash.
Martin's the highest at 16%, then me at
11. Vincent at almost 11. Uh Melvin got
his way back up to 9. John, who used to
be the one holding the most cash by like
a large sum. He's like what 25% is now
down to just 1.6. He's almost broke uh
as Clarity doesn't get past. So, we'll
see what happens there. But I will talk
about crypto in a second. But um
but anyway, I just wanted to share that.
Uh Melvin, you wanted to add something
on
>> No, I literally was going to comment on
John's cash position. I think he's fully
invested in as of like a couple days
ago. So, um I I just thought it was it
was kind of funny. I'm going to talk
about crypto in a second, but let me go
over to you first, Vincent. Uh although
maybe you're probably going to to talk
about this as well. Where's your
portfolio right here? You were on
vacation, so maybe you didn't do a whole
lot recently. Um what's on your mind in
terms of your portfolio? You looking to
do anything?
>> I was on vacation, but I was checking
markets daily, of course. Um
I really was actually I was with my dad
walking and he was asking me, "What are
you doing on your phone your entire
[laughter] time?" And I was showing him
X and he was like, "What the fuck?"
Anyways, um so my view hasn't really
changed over the last two weeks. Um I'm
not going to deploy any new capital
capital into the AI infiltrate. Probably
shifting around some of my capital,
moving some out of uh GLW or Corning
into into some of the names that I think
have a more clear path towards the next
earning spike. I think that's Bloom
Energy, Micron, and Infinian. Especially
Infinian is like going to prices or to
levels now which are really interesting
to me. Market is like fully selling off
the name. I think not really
understanding the story of power
semiconductors in 800 volt DC and
especially the involvement of um
Infinion in the space. So that's one
side of things. The other side of things
I have a pretty strong view is the whole
digital assets space. You mentioned
Clarity Act today really important.
Let's see how that plays out. But um
even if it were a no and they were not
passing, I think it would be a short to
midterm bummer in the space. I would be
buying dips there. I would be buying
hood. I would be buying ETH. Uh don't
have a really strong view on altcoins
though. I think it makes sense for John
to to start investing here because he's
really deep in the space and I think
there's alpha to be made here. So, I
wouldn't be surprised if John end of the
year, beginning of next year is by far
in number one because alt alts are
starting to outperform, but we shall
see. Um, yeah, and Robin Hood is is is
what still one of my biggest conviction
names here. I think the the the teases
and this is really telling Tim. I wanted
to to make this point on the on the pot
earlier. We're doing like the pots that
are performing or the posts on social
media perform are all about AI
infrastructure mainly. If you're talking
about agentic AI, AI adoption, the the
teases of AI agents at Robin Hood, for
instance, the market and people do not
really care. And this to me is just
telling that this is this teas is really
early and is is only starting to play
out. So, so remaining very bullish on in
in that space and and adding dips there
with with new capital.
>> Nice. Yeah, for me, I I I sold um my
Salesforce position. I was up 60% or so.
Um, so I just sold the whole thing. Um,
I still have my kind of SAS exposure
through Service Now. Um, although it's
quite small at this point and now I
think Salesforce is up a little bit
today. Uh, you know, we're going back to
the same thing. When infrastructure goes
down, software goes up. So that's kind
of how it's split out. But either way,
um, what I'm really eyeing up right now
is if I don't think the Clarity Act is
going to get passed, um, which by the
way is just the the regulation around
the crypto industry. It looks like it's
not going to get passed. My hope is that
as a result, Bitcoin is going to kind of
nuke much lower. If I actually pull up
the chart, by the way, we talked about
this, me and John, there's an after
hours going on from the crypto side, uh,
probably today on the same day. Um, so I
would just watch there, we go in more
detail. I have a feeling we're going to
come back down here and if this does,
Galaxy, um, Robin Hood, uh, Coinbase, a
lot of the the crypto equities that
we've talked about that kind of stretch
into also AI and Aentic, I think they're
going to nuke along with it. Uh even IN
uh and I think Wolf they were a bitcoin
miner as well right wolf financial
>> iron yes yes uh wol but they are not
mining anymore. Yeah.
>> Okay. So one thing to understand about
even Iran is their their price currently
moves on on the price of Bitcoin because
that's still their biggest revenue
stream is is mining Bitcoin. And so I
think a lot of these companies that are
moving into the AI space pivoting and
and are well positioned there. They're
still moving off the backs of crypto.
It's why they've done so well over the
last few weeks. We've talked a ton about
this. Um, I don't know what's going to
happen here, but if Clarity doesn't get
packed, my hope is that Bitcoin is going
to have a bit of a nuke. Um, and then I
think it's all going to bounce back
because what's going to happen is the
CFTC and the SEC are already ready to
release regulations regardless of the
Clarity Act. So, they don't need it. I
think they're going to release by the
end of the week if Clarity Act doesn't
get passed. Um, and I think we're going
to see a quick dip and then things will
go back up and and I'm not overly
concerned. It'd be nice to have Clarity
Act, don't get me wrong. I just don't
think we need it. Uh, and so I'm hoping
that I can get Galaxy, maybe Coin, uh,
you know, a little bit lower off of the
backs of that. So, I don't know if it's
going to happen, but that's kind of one
of the reasons why I'm kind of holding
out cash right now and kind of sitting
in. I think last week I said I wanted to
buy Galaxy. It was at like 26 or 27. I
was like, I'm just going to hold out for
a bit here. And we're at 22.8 right now.
Hopefully, it can go a little bit lower
and I' I'd look to buy more.
>> What makes you think that the Clarity
Act is not that important? I mean like
you know uh CEO of Coinbase, CEO of
Galaxy, they are all in Washington just
lobbying to get this bill passed through
and yet it seems like it's not. So I
feel like
>> all the people involved really want this
bill to go through and so I feel like it
is important to the whole industry.
>> It it is 100% important. I'm not saying
it's not important, but Clarity Act,
really what it is is a bunch of rules to
say that the regulators need to get a
framework and a regulatory framework uh
live. That's what they're trying to make
a law here. And the regulatory companies
that are involved in crypto are already
saying, "Hey, we don't even need
clarity. We're going to do it anyway."
And they've already been saying that
they're prepared to launch their their
regulatory um infrastructure or sorry,
their regulatory framework even if Clare
doesn't pass. So, of course, it would be
amazing if it did. it would help a lot
of institutions get into the space and
and build in blockchain um with more
clarity. But I think we're going to get
some clarity regardless even if we don't
get it. And Brian Armstrong was the one
who said that. Mike Noatz really wants
it. Brian Armstrong was like, even if we
don't get it, it's fine. We're going to
get reg regulation anyway. So, I don't
know. It's it's obviously not great, but
I don't think it's like the end of the
world if it doesn't come through. I
think um I think we'll be all right. So,
let's see. That's kind of my my take
there. All right, guys. Any um we got a
couple more minutes. Anyone else eyeing
anything else that we should be talking
about here?
>> Yeah, something I was mentioning on on
the pod earlier is um is Bending Spoons.
I'm going to do a deep dive on YouTube
this week, so you get the full teases
there.
>> That's a public company.
>> It's a public company. They did their
IPO in June or something June or May. Um
>> what's the ticker?
>> BSP. BSP. It's a Yeah, as I said, the
CEO is framing it this way. It's a 75%
tech company, 25% private equity
company. And the their playbook, their
AI enabled playbook is crazy. They're
buying stuff and they have 50 different
AI enabled tools which they bring to
just cut out costs of the companies,
enhance their products. So, it's a yeah,
it's a it's it's it's a not well-known
company. I mean, none of you guys know
it. I think um I I checked on X. Just a
couple of people are talking about this
company. Stock is not that up a lot. Um
it's yeah, it's it's a really
interesting play that I uh I definitely
have on my watch list here.
>> There was um our PR guy kept asking me
about this. Um so I think some of the
news like media companies uh or outlets,
sorry, were were kind of onto this, but
maybe that was around their IPO because
I kept saying I don't know. I haven't
looked enough into it and so I didn't
never gave like a take on it but um it
has died out since then because he
hasn't asked in a while. Yeah, I'm just
I'm I'm just really bullish on the
broader AI adoption space because I
think we're reaching a level of Jansen
calls it AGI now where the model
capability is just so high. It's just
now all about adoption, right? And I
posted this chart on X today where where
you see that the AI adopting companies
are outperforming the nonAI adopting
companies like especially like there
there's building this wedge and I think
this is coming from this enhanced
capabilities and everything from Eli Liy
to Robin Hood to to Bending Spoons I
think are great buys because this thesis
is not built in yet and it's starting to
play out.
>> It's the application layer. I I continue
to look for more opportunities there.
This is why I'm talking about Coinbase
and Robin Hood uh at same idea. Eli Liy
actually just had um a price target
raised up to 1,400. I forget which bank
it was. Um and so you know it's only at
what 1100 right now. So it's starting to
get raises. I think application and this
is what Martin's portfolio is right.
Apploving Uber these are all application
layer stuffed AI where it's going to
reinvent their business um and hopefully
make them much more profitable um and
increase their earnings. I'm actually
like really bullish on that layer who is
going to bring that you know ROI on AI
because not every company is able to
really build AI agents in an effective
way so their business is getting better.
So you know some companies they should
just not even try that and just
outsource that part of their business.
So like you know I think Salesforce or
service now because they are so so much
integrated in across all S&P 500
companies that's pretty easy for them to
just hey we are going to sell you this
agent and this agent and like you know
eventually this is going to be the
orchestration layer for the companies
who are not capable of building that
orchestration for themselves.
>> I still think Palanteer is a is a great
buy for exactly for this
>> these levels though. Come on. It's at
180 190 I think. What is it at right
now?
>> I I I really don't care. I really don't
care about the valuation of this
company. This was this company was never
never never never cheap. It's it's the
complete opposite of the AI
infrastructure trade which is really
cheap at the moment. It's just a thesis
that they're going to be the ones
deploying AI and especially agentic AI
at companies at a in a way that is
affordable for companies. That's teases
on Palunteer.
>> I get it. But PE ratio of 147 is a
little [laughter] too steep, man.
>> I mean, you're only Tesla. What's the PE
ratio of Tesla?
>> What is it? 300.
>> Even worse, that's they have a harder
but yeah.
>> Martin, what's your view on Palunteer,
though? I'm interested.
>> I have love and hate relationship with
Bondier.
>> I think it's awesome company and I want
to
Yeah, I I just struggle to buy at this
prices.
>> But like I agree with you, Winston. Like
I'm usually the one who says like, "Hey,
it's [ __ ] expensive." But again, I
think you could apply this for Tesla as
well. And I think Ponteer is really
exceptional here. So I'm really
considering to to buy some volunteer
actually because I just love that
business and I just need to make my mind
about the current prices. But you you
also express that same trade through
Service Now, right? It's a very similar
somewhat similar company. Also a high
valuation but not nowhere near as high
as Palanteer and it got sold off like
crazy. You bought it back in was it June
near the lows or maybe even a little
before that like under 100 bucks or
around 100 bucks. Um and that's paid
off. It's at 144 now, right? So, you
already kind of have exposure to the the
harness AI trade already.
>> I want more exposure to that layer.
>> Yeah, I agree. It's just value.
>> Sell some Galaxy, bro. Sell some Galaxy.
[laughter]
>> Never.
>> All right, guys. Let's wrap there. But
thanks for that was a great after hours.
Uh appreciate everyone for for joining
in. Uh a reminder, you can go connect
your portfolios uh now inside of Milk
Road Pro. It'll pull in all your your
own assets and you can compare them
beside our analysts. Uh we'll soon have
an insights tab as well where our
analysts will be able to give insights
on your portfolio uh through AI of
course uh and through all the data of of
our research and training. So it's going
to be super cool. So go connect, check
out the new features and um we'll be
launching a bunch more soon. But thanks
everyone for joining in. Take care.
>> Thanks guys.
>> Bye guys.
>> Thanks for listening to Milk Road.
[music] If you enjoyed the show, make
sure you like and subscribe. And if
you're struggling to find winners in the
market, that's exactly what Milkro Pro
is built for. Our analysts have called
some of the biggest winners early and
Pro lets you see what they're [music]
buying next, every trade they make, and
the research behind every position.
Check out Milk Road Pro at the link
below. Everything you hear on Milk Road
is forformational purposes only. These
are our personal opinions, not financial
advice, and we may own some of the
investments we talk about. Always do
your own research and make the decisions
that are right for you. See you next
time.